(birds chirping)
♪ Wake up in the mornin'
feelin' like P Diddy ♪
♪ Hey, what up girl ♪
♪ Grab my glasses, I'm out the
door, I'm gonna hit this city ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Before I leave, brush my
teeth with a bottle of Jack ♪
♪ 'Cause when I leave for the
night, I ain't comin' back ♪
♪ I'm talkin' pedicure on our toes, toes ♪
♪ Tryin' on all our clothes, clothes ♪
♪ Boys blowin' up our phones, phones ♪
♪ Drop-toppin', playin' our favorite CDs ♪
♪ Pullin' up to the parties ♪
♪ Tryna get a little bit tipsy ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Ain't got a care in the
world, but got plenty of beer ♪
♪ Ain't got no money in my
pocket, but I'm already here ♪
♪ And now the dudes are linin' up ♪
♪ 'Cause they hear we got swagger ♪
♪ But we kick 'em to the curb ♪
♪ Unless they look like Mick Jagger ♪
♪ I'm talkin' 'bout everybody
gettin' crunk, crunk ♪
♪ Boys try to touch my junk, junk ♪
♪ Gonna smack him if he
gettin' too drunk, drunk ♪
♪ Now, now, we go until
they kick us out, out ♪
♪ Or the police shut us down, down ♪
♪ Police shut us down, down ♪
♪ Po-po shut us down ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ DJ, you build me up ♪
♪ You break me down ♪
♪ My heart, it pounds ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me ♪
♪ With my hands up ♪
♪ You got me now ♪
♪ You got that sound ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me ♪
♪ DJ, you build me up ♪
♪ You break me down ♪
♪ My heart, it pounds ♪
♪ Yeah, you got me ♪
♪ With my hands up ♪
♪ Put your hands up ♪
♪ Now, the party don't
start 'til I walk in ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Don't stop, make it pop ♪
♪ DJ, blow my speakers up ♪
♪ Tonight, I'ma fight ♪
♪ 'Til we see the sunlight ♪
♪ Tik tok on the clock ♪
♪ But the party don't stop, no ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, whoa-oh ♪
(Kesha laughing)
(speaking in foreign language)